Consumers' League of New York City Records 5307
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
- CL Administrative, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 17)
  Miscellaneous Routine correspondence
- Agricultural Labor - Camp Conditions, 1947 (Box 5, Folder 18)
  Reports on Smyra Camp conditions
- Agricultural Labor - Camp Sanitary Code, 1944 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Agricultural Labor - Child Labor on Farms - NYS Dept. of Labor, 1947-1948 (Box 5, Folder 20)
  Includes pamphlet and one letter with enclosed list of child care centers
- Agricultural Labor - Committee on Migrant Camps, NYS War Council, 1945 (Box 5, Folder 21)
  Reports and correspondence
- Agricultural Labor - Correspondence, 1947-1948 (Box 5, Folder 22)
  Includes correspondence and reports re migrant camps
- Agricultural Labor - Employment of Non-Farm Youth, 1943-1945 (Box 5, Folder 23)
  Includes publications, correspondence and reports
- Agricultural Labor - Foreign Workers, 1944-1945 (Box 5A, Folder 1)
  Correspondence re imported farm labor
- Agricultural Labor - Health, 1944-1946 (Box 5A, Folder 2)
  Reports and pamphlets
- Agricultural Labor - Legislation - Connecticut, 1945 (Box 5A, Folder 3)
  Transportation and employment of minors
- Agricultural Labor - Legislation - New Jersey, 1943-1945 (Box 5A, Folder 4)
- Agricultural Labor - Legislation - New York State, 1945-1948 (Box 5A, Folder 5)
  Includes reports and correspondence
- Agricultural Labor - Medical Care for Migrants, 1945-1946 (Box 5A, Folder 6)
- Agricultural Labor - Migrants - N.Y.S. Interdepartmental Committee on Migrant Labor Includes reports and correspondence, 1946- 1947 (Box 5A, Folder 7)
- Agricultural Labor - Migrants Presidents Commission Statement and correspondence, 1950 (Box 5A, Folder 8)
- Agricultural Labor - Migrant Camps Publications and correspondence, 1946-1947 (Box 5A, Folder 9)
- Agricultural Labor - Migrant Camp Reports, 1944-1946 (Box 5A, Folder 10)
- Agricultural Labor - Migrant Children Care Centers Correspondence and report, 1945 (Box 5A, Folder 11)
- Agricultural Labor - Migrant Children Education, 1945 (Box 5A, Folder 12)
- Agricultural Labor - Migrant Children Correspondence with E. Corsi, N.Y.S. Industrial Commissioner, reports and publications, 1940-1946 (Box 5A, Folder 13)
- Agricultural Labor - Migrant Children Correspondence, 1947-1948 (Box 5A, Folder 14)
- Agricultural Labor - Migrant Program Correspondence, 1944-1946 (Box 5A, Folder 15)
  Includes correspondence and releases
- Agricultural Labor - Migrant Program, 1945 (Box 5A, Folder 16)
- Agricultural Labor - National Citizens Council for Migrant Labor, 1948 (Box 5A, Folder 17)
- Agricultural Labor - New Jersey, 1945 (Box 5A, Folder 18)
- Agricultural Labor - NYS Legislation Motor Vehicle and Traffic Law, 1945 (Box 5A, Folder 19)
- Agricultural Labor - Other Organizations Publications, form letters, 1944-1949 (Box 5A, Folder 20)
- Agricultural Labor - Pictures (Box 5A, Folder 21)
- Agricultural Labor - Placement Operations, 1943 (Box 5B, Folder 1)
  Report NYC Farm Office Includes report entitled "War-Time Harvest"
- Agricultural Labor - Proposed Legislation by Consumers League, 1944-1947 (Box 5B, Folder 2)
- Agricultural Labor - Proposed Legislation, Federal, 1947 (Box 5B, Folder 3)
- Agricultural Labor - Publicity, 1945-1948 (Box 5B, Folder 4)
- Agricultural Labor - Rochester Conference, 1945 (Box 5B, Folder 5)
  Notes and reports
- Agricultural Labor - State-Wide Citizens Committee on Seasonal Farm Labor Minutes and correspondence, 1945 (Box 5B, Folder 6)
- Agricultural Labor - State Department of Labor Release and publication entitled "Seasonal Labor on Fruit and Vegetable Farms NYS, 1945" (Box 5B, Folder 7)
- Agricultural Labor - Wages and Expenses, 1945 (Box 5B, Folder 8)
- Agricultural Labor - Wartime Use of Women publications by U.S. Women's Bureau, 1942-1943 (Box 5B, Folder 9)
- Agricultural Labor - Youth Employment War Dispensation Correspondence, 1945 (Box 5B, Folder 10)
- Agriculture - Federal Labor Legislation, 1947 (Box 5B, Folder 11)
- Agriculture - Health of Migrant Workers, 1944-1945 (Box 5B, Folder 12)
- Agriculture - Migrants - Union Reporter, 1945 (Box 5B, Folder 13)
  Three issues of Reporter
- Agriculture, 1952-1957 (Box 5B, Folder 14)
  Includes form letter re migrant labor, supporting statement to amend labor law in re licensing contractors supplying farm workers, release on Ten Point Program
- Agriculture - Statewide Citizens Committee on Seasonal Farm Labor, 1945-1947 (Box 5B, Folder 15)
- Annual Meetings, 1945-1958 (Box 5B, Folder 16)
  Includes minutes of annual membership meetings
- Annual Reports, 1910-1928 (Box 5B, Folder 17)
- Annual and Other Reports (Box 5B, Folder 18)
  1930s; Contains resolutions, report of Reorganization Committee Secretary's report, 1939
- Bequests to League, 1913-1941 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  Copies of wills and correspondence re bequests
- Board (CL) - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1946-1950 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  Board of Directors minutes, correspondence with committee members
- Board Meetings Announcement of meetings, 1945-1946 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Board Members - Correspondence - General, 1944-1946 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  Routine correspondence
- Board of Directors - General Correspondence, 1944-1947 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  Correspondence re meetings and migrant camp problems
- Board of Directors - Memos and Notices, 1944-1948 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  Contains announcements of meetings, cancellations, reports of various committees
- Board of Directors - Resignations, Nominations, etc, 1945-1947 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Board of Directors Executive Committee, 1944-1946 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  Contains correspondence, resolutions and minutes
- Board of Directors - Executive Committee Minutes, 1945-1950 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Board of Directors - Executive Committee Minutes, 1945 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Board of Directors Minutes (Box 6A, Folder 1)
- Board of Directors Executive Committee - Minutes, 1921-1934 (Box 6A, Folder 2)
- Board of Directors Executive Committee - Minutes, 1938-1945 (Box 6B, Folder 1)
- Board of Directors and Executive Committee - Minutes, 1948-1950 (Box 6B, Folder 2)
- Board of Directors and Executive Committee - Minutes, 1950-1958 (Box 6B, Folder 3)
- Board of Directors - Miscellaneous Correspondence, 1951-1954 (Box 6B, Folder 4)
  Includes report by Mrs. Robert Morris on meeting of Suffolk County Council of Churches' Migrant Committee
- Board of Directors - Contributions, 1945-1947 (Box 6B, Folder 5)
- Board of Directors - Correspondence, 1955 (Box 6B, Folder 6)
  Includes correspondence re experimental school for children of migrants, list of Board of Directors, routine correspondence
- Board of Directors - Correspondence, 1956 (Box 6B, Folder 7)
- Board of Directors - Correspondence, 1957 (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Board of Directors - Correspondence, 1958 (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Board of Directors - Correspondence, 1959 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Board of Directors - Correspondence, 1960 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Board of Directors - Form Letters, 1948-1950 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  Includes minutes for Dec. 7, 1948, resolution, and prospectus
- Board of Directors - Form Letters, 1950-1956 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  Includes statement re safety regulations for children working on farms, executive secretary report 1951-52, migrant labor study and summary of findings, draft platform statement, 1951-52
- Board of Directors - Form Letters, 1956 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  Includes Board of Directors Minutes, Oct. 23, 1957
- Board of Directors - Minutes of Meetings, 1944-1947 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Board of Directors -Nominations, Elections and Resignations, 1945-1948 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  Includes reports, minutes, correspondence
- Board of Directors and Executive Committee - Minutes of Meetings - 1951-53, 1951-1953 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Board of Directors - Minutes of Meetings - 1954-58, 1954-1958 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Board of Directors - Minutes of Meetings - 1959-61, 1959-1961 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- Board of Directors - Nominations, Elections and Resignations, 1947-1948 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Board of Directors - nominations, Elections and Resignations, 1948-1950 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  Includes list of directors and officers, minutes, routine correspondence
- Board of Directors - Nominations, Elections and Resignations, 1950-1951 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Board of Directors - Nominations, Elections, and Resignations, 1951-1952 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Board of Directors - Nominations, Elections, and Resignations, 1952-1953 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Board of Directors - Nominations, Elections and Resignations, 1953-1954 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Board of Directors - Nominations, Elections and Resignations, 1954-1955 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Board of Directors - Nominations, Elections, and Resignations, 1955-1956 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Board of Directors - Nominations. Elections and Resignations, 1956-1957 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Board of Directors - Nominations, Elections, and Resignations, 1957-1958 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Board of Directors - Nominations, Elections and Resignations, 1958-1960 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Candy White List Publications (Box 8A, Folder 1)
- Child Labor - Federal Legislation Releases, statements, publications, 1945-1950 (Box 8A, Folder 2)
- Child Labor - General, 1947-1948 (Box 8A, Folder 3)
- Child Labor - General, 1945-1946 (Box 8A, Folder 4)
- Child Labor Laws Correspondence re legislation, publications, 1949-1951 (Box 8A, Folder 5)
- Child Labor - Newsboys Notes, correspondence, publications, 1935-1946 (Box 8A, Folder 6)
- Child Labor - N.Y.S. Legislation, 1944-1950 (Box 8A, Folder 7)
- Child Labor - State Standards Publication, 1946 (Box 8A, Folder 8)
  182pp
- Child Labor - Truck Farms Pamphlet, 1939 (Box 8A, Folder 9)
- Christinas Shopping Campaign Publicity (Box 8A, Folder 10)
- Church Groups Routine correspondences, 1958 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Committees - Child Labor, 1959 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- Committees - Executives, 1949-1959 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- Committees - Executive, 1948-1950 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  Minutes, agenda
- Committees - Farm Labor Committee, 1958 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  Contains minutes, memo sent to Gov. Rockefeller concerning migrant farm labor, reports
- Committees - Health and Housing of Migrant Workers, 1956-1957 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  Includes report on sanitary conditions in small migrant labor camps
- Committee on Appointment of Labor Commissioner, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Committees - Labor Department - Sub-Committee, 1947 (Box 9, Folder 8)
- Committees - Legislative Includes Report and Analysis of Women's Trade Union League Legislative Program, 1946-1947 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Committees - Membership Minutes, financial statements, 1950-1953 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Committees - Program, 1947 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  Includes minutes
- Committees - Program and Budget, 1954 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  Includes letter to Senator Irving Ives
- Committees - Promotion Includes correspondence re fund raising for CL, 1946-1948 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- Conference with George M. Shapiro, 1953 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  Nov. 1953 Correspondence re migrant labor
- Consumers League (Box 9, Folder 15)
  Historical Includes photographs, correspondence 1914-1945, letters to and from President Woodrow Wilson
- Consumers League (Box 9, Folder 16)
  1920s; Includes historical summary of CL activities entitled "Pages from the CL Scrapbook", 1896-1926; legislative program, 1926-30 and minutes, 1929
- Consumers League (Box 9, Folder 17)
  1930s; Program for 1939-40, various reports, minutes, correspondence, chronology of activities 1896-1930, articles
- Consumers League (Box 9, Folder 18)
  1940s; Includes copies of speeches by E.M. Herrick, Executive Secretary; correspondence, memo on purpose and general program
- Consumers League - Annual Meeting, 1945 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  Correspondence re meeting, minutes, lists of officers and Board of Directors
- Consumers League - Annual Meeting, 1946 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  Includes form letters
- Consumers League - Connecticut, 1944-1946 (Box 9, Folder 21)
- Consumers League - Michigan, 1944-1946 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  Includes scattered Issues of "CL of Michigan Bulletin," routine correspondence
- Consumers League - New Jersey, 1944-1946 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  Includes correspondences publication, releases
- Consumers League - Other states, 1961 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  Includes statement for the CL of lew Jersey concerning education, CL of N.J. constitution and an analysis of migratory labor bills
- Cost of Living, 1943-1946 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  Publications
- Disability Insurance (Box 9, Folder 26)
  Includes publications, bills and related correspondence 1947-51
- Domestic Service, 1944-1946 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  Publications, correspondence
- Executive Secretary, 1944-1946 (Box 9A, Folder 1)
- Financial - Contribution Receipts, 1947 (Box 9A, Folder 2)
- Financial - Membership Acknowledgements, etc., 1944-1946 (Box 9A, Folder 3)
- Financial - Reports and Statements, 1944-1946 (Box 9A, Folder 4)
- Financial Reports, 1919-1926 (Box 9A, Folder 5)
- Financial - Amalgamated Bank, 1947-1953 (Box 9A, Folder 6)
- Financial - Balance Sheets and Statements Audit reports, 1941-1947 (Box 9A, Folder 7)
- Financial - Bequests, 1952 (Box 9A, Folder 8)
- Financial - Income Tax Exemption, 1935-1954 (Box 9A, Folder 9)
- Financial - Loans to League, 1951 (Box 9A, Folder 10)
- Financial - Budget, 1947-1948 (Box 9A, Folder 11)
- Financial - Social Security Federal and state income tax forms, 1946-1952 (Box 9A, Folder 12)
- Format - Appeal, 1945-1948 (Box 9A, Folder 13)
- Format - CL Distribution Includes correspondence re pamphlets dealing with migratory labor, 1946-1947 (Box 9A, Folder 14)
- Format - Invitations, 1947 (Box 9A, Folder 15)
  1947 Fall meeting
- Format - Letterhead, 1946-1947 (Box 9A, Folder 16)
- Format - Renewal, 1946-1948 (Box 9A, Folder 17)
- Government Agencies - N.Y.S. Dept. of Labor, Division of Women in Industry and Minimum Wage, 1943-1945 (Box 9A, Folder 18)
- Industrial Homework Publications re child labor in tenements, 1908-1939 (Box 9A, Folder 19)
- Industrial Homework - Enforcement Correspondence, 1945-1946 (Box 9A, Folder 20)
- Industrial Homework - Labor Standards Conference Report, 1934 (Box 9A, Folder 21)
- Industrial Homework - N.Y.S. Labor Department Reports Publications, 1944 (Box 9A, Folder 22)
- Industrial Homework - Public Hearings (Box 9A, Folder 23)
- Inquiries, 1944-1946 (Box 9B, Folder 1)
  Requests for information re quality and prices of goods
- Inquiries, 1947 (Box 9B, Folder 2)
  Requests for publications
- Inventory - Books - Pamphlets, 1945 (Box 9B, Folder 3)
- Joads Study - Camps Visited, 1945 (Box 9B, Folder 4)
  Lists of camps
- Joads Study - Camp Investigation Reports #1, 1945 (Box 9B, Folder 5)
  Forms
- Joads Study - Camp Investigation Reports #2, 1945 (Box 9B, Folder 6)
- Joads Study - Camp Investigation Reports #3, 1944-1945 (Box 9B, Folder 7)
- Joads Study - Distribution Forms Form letters, 1946 (Box 9B, Folder 8)
- Joads Study - Extract in 'Magazine Digest', 1945 (Box 9B, Folder 9)
  Correspondence re article
- Joads Study - 'Joads' Rough Drafts, 1944-1946 (Box 9B, Folder 10)
- Joads Study - Newspaper Clippings, 1945-1946 (Box 9B, Folder 11)
- Joads Study - Pamphlet Acknowledgements and Comments, 1944-1946 (Box 9B, Folder 12)
- Joads Study - Pamphlet Complimentary Copies, 1945 (Box 9B, Folder 13)
- Joads Study - Pamphlet Distribution, Executive Board, 1945 (Box 9B, Folder 14)
- Joads Study - Pamphlet Distribution, 1945-1946 (Box 9B, Folder 15)
- Joads Study - Pamphlet Distribution #2, 1947-1948 (Box 9C, Folder 1)
- Joads Study - Pamphlet Illustration (Box 9C, Folder 2)
- Joads Study - Pamphlet Publicity Sartain Correspondence, 1945 (Box 9C, Folder 3)
- Joads Study - Pamphlet Publicity, 1945 (Box 9C, Folder 4)
- Joads Study - Reports (Drafts), 1944-1946 (Box 9C, Folder 5)
- Joads Study - Requests for Reviews, Notices, etc., 1946-1947 (Box 9C, Folder 6)
- Joads, What Next - Camp Reports, Forms, 1945 (Box 9C, Folder 7)
- Joads, What Next - Study Reports, 1945 (Box 9C, Folder 8)
- Labor Organizations - CIO Textile Workers Union, 1945 (Box 9C, Folder 9)
- Labor Organizations - CIO United Electrical, Radio and Machine Workers of America, 1945 (Box 9C, Folder 10)
- Labor Organizations - Laundry Workers Joint Board, 1945 (Box 9C, Folder 11)
- Legislation - Federal, 1944-1946 (Box 9C, Folder 12)
  Equal Rights Amendment Publications, announcements, releases
- Legislation - Federal, 1944-1946 (Box 9C, Folder 13)
  U.S. Employment Service
- Legislation - N.Y.S. Equal Pay Law, 1945-1946 (Box 9C, Folder 14)
- Legislation - N.Y.S. Household Employees, 1945 (Box 9C, Folder 15)
- Legislation - N.Y.S., 1945 (Box 9C, Folder 16)
- Legislation - N.Y.S. - Workmen's Compensation, 1946 (Box 9C, Folder 17)
- Legislation - Position of Organization Other than CL, 1945-1946 (Box 9C, Folder 18)
- Legislative Committee Statement to Jt. Legislative Committee on Industrial and Labor Conditions, 1945 (Box 9C, Folder 19)
  12/14/45 Correspondence with committee members
- Letters to League Members, 1945 (Box 9C, Folder 20)
  Form letters
- Membership, 1940-1941 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  Lists
- Membership Correspondence, 1944 (Box 10, Folder 2)
- Membership Correspondence, 1945 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  January 1945-May 1945 Resignations, appointments, contributions, etc.
- Membership Correspondence, 1945 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  June 1945-December 1945
- Membership Correspondence, 1946 (Box 10, Folder 5)
- Membership Correspondence - Kelley, Florence M., 1945 (Box 10, Folder 6)
- Membership Correspondence - Woodruff, Katherine, 1944-1945 (Box 10, Folder 7)
- Membership - Prospects Lists, correspondence, 1943-1947 (Box 10, Folder 8)
- Membership - Prospects Correspondence, 1945 (Box 10, Folder 9)
- Membership and Appeals, 1946-1959 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  Correspondence Re dues, contributions and resignations
- Membership Correspondence, Miscellaneous, 1951-1959 (Box 10, Folder 11)
- Membership Appeal Letters, 1934-1938 (Box 10, Folder 12)
- Membership Appeal Letters, 1938-1942 (Box 10, Folder 13)
- Membership Appeal Letters, 1945-1948 (Box 10, Folder 14)
- Membership Appeal Letters, 1949-1951 (Box 10, Folder 15)
- Membership Appeal Letters for Special Contributions, 1953-1954 (Box 10A, Folder 1)
- Membership Appeal Letters - Helen Gahagan Douglas, 1958 (Box 10A, Folder 2)
- Membership and Appeals - Form Acknowledgement Letters, 1947-1959 (Box 10A, Folder 3)
- Membership and Appeals - Form Letters for New Members, 1948-1960 (Box 10A, Folder 4)
- Membership and Appeals - Form Letters to (Other Than Appeals), 1947-1958 (Box 10A, Folder 5)
- Membership and Appeals - Form Membership Renewal Letters, 1947-1960 (Box 10A, Folder 6)
- Membership and Appeals - Special Hernik Appeal, 1947 (Box 10A, Folder 7)
  Includes routine replies re appeal letter
- Membership and Appeals - Individual Appeals and Acknowledgements, 1951-1960 (Box 10A, Folder 8)
- Membership and Appeals, 1951 (Box 10A, Folder 9)
  May 1951 Special Letter to Members Asking that They Double Dues Rate Includes form letter plus draft and replies
- Membership and Appeals for Migrant Labor Survey, 1959 (Box 10A, Folder 10)
- Membership and Appeals - Prospects Includes lists of prospects, 1945-1948 (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Membership and Appeals - Special Contributions for Migrant Labor legislative Campaign, 1958 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  Includes routine correspondence and leaflet entitled "End Feudalism on the Farms"
- Membership and Appeals - Trade Unions, 1958-1959 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Membership and Appeals - Westchester Event, 1952 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  Spring 1952 Includes routine correspondence and financial report
- Nominating Committee, 1945-1946 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Personnel, 1944-1946 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Personnel Committee (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Personnel Includes policies, resumes, correspondence, 1946-1956 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Program and Budget Committee (Ann Montero, Chairman), 1954 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  Includes minutes, financial statement
- Promotion - Foundations, 1945 (Box 11, Folder 10)
- Promotion - Membership Drive Through Board Members, 1945-1946 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  Includes correspondence with Professor Jean MeKelvey
- Promotion - Return on Appeals, Statistics, 1944-1946 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- Promotion - Rochester Conferences, 1945 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  March 22, 1945
- Promotion - Rochester Conference Correspondence, 1945 (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Promotion and Publicity - Luncheon - Public Stake in Wage Policy and Agricultural Migrants, 1947 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  Jan. 8, 1947
- Promotion and Publicity - News Releases, 1950-1954 (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Promotion and Publicity - Press Clippings, 1952-1953 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Publications - Ad Hoc Conference on Migrant Farm Labor Reports, 1958 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  Jan-58
- Publications - 'End Feudalism on the Farms', 1958 (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Publications - 'The Consumers League of New York - 56 Years on the Forefront of the Movement', 1947 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Publications - 'Consumers League of New York - 57 Years of Leadership Toward Better Labor Standards', 1948 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Publications - Joads (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Publications - Migrant Labor Miscellaneous (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Publications - 'The Community Looks At Migrant Labor' Publication, 1959 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Publications - Newsletter comments requests for additional copies, etc., 1950-1952 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Publications - Newsletter Correspondence re preparation of newsletter; drafts of articles for newsletter, 1950-1953 (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Publications - 'About Your Labor Laws' Distribution, 1948 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Publications - Newsletter, 1947-1952 (Box 12, Folder 16-20)
- Publications - Newsletter, 1951 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  June 1951 Replies to questionnaire
- Publications - Newsletter, 1952-1953 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  Series 10
- Publications - Newsletter, 1953-1954 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  Series 11
- Publications - Newsletter, 1954-1955 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  Series 12
- Publications - Newsletter, 1955-1956 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  Series 13
- Publications - Newsletter, 1956-1957 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  Series 14
- Publications - Newsletter, 1957-1958 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  Series 15
- Publications - Newsletter, 1958-1959 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  Series 16
- Publications - Newsletter, 1959-1960 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  Series 17
- Publications - Other Includes drafts of publications, 1948-1949 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Publications - 'Sweatshops in the Sun' Includes several copies of publication, 1952 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Advisory Council on Employment and Unemployment Insurance, 1957 (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Allied Printing Trades Council (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Amalgamated Clothing Workers of America, 1959-1960 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  Includes correspondence re migrant labor story
- American Civil Liberties Union, 1944-1958 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- American Parents Committee, Inc., 1956 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  Includes correspondence re children under 16 operating farm machinery
- Amityvllle Race Relations Class, 1957-1959 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  Includes report on migratory camps of Long Island
- Apfel and Englander - Auditors Reports of auditors, 1949-1959 (Box 14, Folder 7)
- Appeals - Scheiber Appeal, 1957 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  December 1957 Includes mailing lists, draft of letter
- Attorney General Lefkowitz, 1958 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  Includes correspondence, summary of legislative program
- Baden Street Settlement, 1955-1958 (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Bridgehampton Child Care Center, 1954-1956 (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Candidates Poll, 1954 (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Central Labor Council of New York City, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  Includes resolution, 1959
- Child Care Centers for Children of Working Mothers -Legislative Action, 1959 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  Includes copies of legislative bills
- Child Labor - Accident Data, 1947-1949 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  Includes correspondence, publications and statistics on accidents, 1947-49